FATHMATH MAYA

ASPIRING DATA ANALYST

Seri Kembangan, Selangor ↑ +601112212036 ****

maaaya.fathmath@gmail.com 🔀

fathmath-maya-9304761b6 in



ABOUT ME

Aspiring Data Analyst with knowledge of relevant technical skills and over 10 years of experience in various business management and administration roles.

I am looking for an opportunity which will challenge my skills and help me grow and drive my career forward.



EDUCATION

MSc in Data Science & Business Analytics

Apr 2022 - Apr 2023 (Expected)

Asia Pacific University of Technology & Innovation

BA (Hons) in International Business Management

Nov 2018 - Nov 2018

CGPA: 3.68

Asia Pacific University of Technology & Innovation

Diploma in Business Management

Nov 2013 - Nov 2014

Clique College



EXPERIENCE

SENIOR OFFICER, ADMINISTRATION

ALLIED INSURANCE COMPANY OF THE MALDIVES

Mar 2017 - Oct 2022

- Daily operations function of the Administration Department Managing & coordinating events, meetings, and travel requirements
- Vendor Negotiations, and Procurement coordination Documentation

OFFICER, ADMINISTRATION & HR

MEGA MALDIVES AIRLINES

Mar 2015 - Feb 2017

- Coordinate and assist with Admin works & HR-related works
- Travel Arrangements
- Other Operational Tasks

MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT, ADMINISTRATION

MALDIVES INDUSTRIAL FISHERIES COMPANY

Mar 2008 - Jun 2014

- Acting as the point of contact for the Managing Director &
- Chairperson among employees, clients, and external partners
- Managing information flow in a timely & accurate manner
- Managing executives' calendars and setting up meetings
- Make travel and accommodation arrangements for Managing Director and Chairperson

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- SAS
- Python
- Google Analytics

- Tableau
- R-programming

LANGUAGES

- English Proficient
- Dhivehi Proficient
- **SKILLS**
 - Project Management
 - Interpersonal Skills
 - Communication

- Teamwork
- Quick Learner

PROJECTS

- Pre-Processing done for DCA charges dataset, KL, This
 project aimed to clean and preprocess the dataset to see if
 there is compliance with local consumer protection and
 licensing regulations. Dataset was prepared and
 preprocessed by SAS.
- Machine Learning Model for Stroke Prediction- This project used R- programming to prepare the dataset, perform EDA, and create machine algorithms for early stroke prediction
- Capstone Project: Clustering machine learning model for enhancing marketing strategies for guesthouses in the Maldives